Ximocu!
西莫库
Stay down, princess. I'll clear the perimeter.
别站起来  公主  我来解决
- Ow! - What happened?
-啊  -怎么了
I think the dome collapsed.
圆顶塌了
- What did you do? - I was trying to protect you.
-你做了什么  -我是想保护你们的
By nearly crushing us?
保护的方式就是差点砸死我们
Okay, that part wasn't supposed to happen.
好吧  不应该发生这事的
but there was a malvago.
但那里有个恶灵
- A who what go? - An evil wizard.
-恶什么玩意儿  -邪恶巫师
He was trying to cast a spell on us.
他想给我们施咒
There's no way an evil wizard could've gotten in the palace.
邪恶巫师不可能进宫殿
I checked everyone.
我检查了所有宾客
Well, there's only one way to find out.
只有一个办法了
We have to get out of here.
我们得出去
- I might have a spell...- Save it.
-我可能有个咒语  -省省吧
I can handle this.
我能搞定
Hm. After you.
嗯  请